# B E N F A N N I N G

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

I am 24 year old politics graduate turned ski instructor turned front-end developer. I attended Le Wagon coding bootcamp in 2017 and was asked to return as a teaching assistant then a teacher. Since then I have taken on a front end position at Hoxton Digital. For more information, check out benfanning.co.uk.

#### CONTACT

07432 495082 fanninggg@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/benfanning-28523315b/

## **EXPERIENCE**

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER | HOXTON-DIGITAL | JUNE 2018 - PRESENT

- Brought about a pivot to mobile focus, due to high demand, resulting in the adoption of React Native as a key language for the company.
- Currently lead front-end developer on an advanced React Native project.

## TEACHER | LE WAGON LONDON | SEPTEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

- Allowed me to dive deeper into the minutia of my lecture subjects to attain a deeper level of understanding of the inner workings of various topics.
- Developed my ability to teach essential coding knowledge at varying levels of understanding, especially on front end topics.

#### TEACHING ASSISTANT | LE WAGON LONDON | MARCH - AUGUST 2018

- Working for the number one ranked coding bootcamp in the world gave me the
  opportunity to redouble my full stack knowledge, as well as refining said knowledge
  by providing explanations of the finer points to students
- Allowed me to review and debug code written in a number of different styles.

## CORE SKILLS

• RUBY

- HTML/CSS
- REACT IS

- RUBY ON RAILS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT NATIVE

## **EDUCATION**

## LE WAGON BOOTCAMP | LONDON | 2017 - 2018

- 9 week intensive program
- Covered the basics of Ruby, Software modelling, Database & SQL, Front End, Rails Framework & AirBnB project, Final project

#### UNIVERSITY OF PLYMOUTH | DEVON | 2012 - 2015

- Bachelor of Arts, 2:1
- Politics & International Relations